<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NovaApp</string>
    
    <!-- Service Types Screen -->
    <string name="select_service_type">Select Service Type</string>
    <string name="select_service_subtype">Select Service Subtype</string>
    
    <!-- Service Types -->
    <string name="cleaning">Cleaning</string>
    <string name="electrical_works">Electrical Works</string>
    <string name="plumbing">Plumbing</string>
    <string name="furniture_repairs">Furniture Repairs</string>
    
    <!-- Cleaning Subtypes -->
    <string name="general_cleaning">General Cleaning</string>
    <string name="deep_cleaning">Deep Cleaning</string>
    <string name="carpet_cleaning">Carpet Cleaning</string>
    <string name="sofa_set_cleaning">Sofa Set Cleaning</string>
    <string name="mattress_cleaning">Mattress Cleaning</string>
    <string name="bathroom_cleaning">Bathroom Cleaning</string>
    <string name="laundry_cleaning">Laundry Cleaning</string>


    <!--General-->
    <string name="kenya_currency_code">KES</string>
    <string name="property_name">Property Name</string>
    <string name="property_address">Property Address</string>
    <string name="service_type">Service Type</string>
    <string name="property_description">Property description</string>
    <string name="property_size">Property Size</string>
    <string name="search_properties">Search properties by name, size, or location…</string>
    <string name="available_properties">My Properties</string>
    <string name="service_name">Service Name</string>
    <string name="base_price">Base Price:</string>
    <string name="preferred_option">Please select your preferred option.</string>
    <string name="option_name">Option Name</string>
    <string name="action_button">Continue</string>
    <string name="my_assets">My Assets</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="jobs">Jobs</string>
    <string name="account">Account</string>
    <string name="manager_name">Manager Name</string>
    <string name="manager_email">Manager Email</string>
    <string name="properties_managing">3 Properties</string>
    <string name="properties">Properties</string>
    <string name="actions">Actions</string>
    <string name="make_payment">Make Payment</string>


    
    <!-- Navigation -->
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="select">Select</string>
    
    <!--Admin nav menu-->
    <string name="nav_home">Home</string>
    <string name="nav_assets">Assets</string>
    <string name="nav_history">History</string>
    <string name="nav_jobs">Jobs</string>
    <string name="nav_account">Account</string>

    <!--Manage assets menu-->
    <string name="nav_add_property">Add Property</string>
    <string name="nav_add_manager">Add Manager</string>


    <!--Admin Home Fragment-->
    <string name="fragment_home">Welcome home</string>
    <string name="active_bookings">Active Bookings</string>
    <string name="available_services">Available Services</string>
    <string name="my_properties">My Properties</string>
    <string name="selected_property">Selected Property</string>
    <string name="book_service">Book Service</string>
    <string name="all_services">All Services</string>
    <string name="start_at">Starts at</string>
    <string name="selected_details">Selected Details</string>
    <string name="select_date">Pick preferred date and time</string>
    <string name="book">Starts at</string>
    <string name="property_details">Property Details</string>
    <string name="manager_details">Manager Details</string>
    <string name="allocated_managers">Allocated Managers</string>
    <string name="add_asset">Add</string>
    <string name="booking_details">Booking Details</string>
    <string name="pending_bill">Pending Bill</string>
    <string name="job_stages">Job Stages</string>
    <string name="add_property">Add Property</string>
    <string name="set_property_type">Select your property type</string>
    <string name="apartment">Apartment</string>
    <string name="bungalow">Bungalow</string>
    <string name="select_property_size_prompt">Select the size of your apartment</string>
    <string name="address_details">Address Details</string>
    <string name="please_fill_details">Provide address details for your property.</string>
    <string name="tap_to_search_using_google_places">Tap to search using Google Places</string>
    <string name="property_size_sq_ft">Property size (sq ft)</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="confirm_details">Confirm Details</string>
    <string name="review_before_submit">Please review and confirm the details below.</string>
    <string name="property_type_and_size">Property type</string>
    <string name="property_size_details">Property size</string>
    <string name="confirm_and_submit">Confirm &amp; submit</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="edit_property_type">Edit property type</string>
    <string name="edit_property_size">Edit property size</string>
    <string name="edit_property_address">Edit property address</string>
    <string name="property_unit_number">Unit Number</string>
    <string name="active_job">Active Job</string>
    <string name="manage_notifications">Manage Notifications</string>
    <string name="about_nova_app">About NovaApp</string>

    <string name="freshchat_app_id">0f9dfe58-b2fe-4734-9dcb-4427b338632c</string>
    <string name="freshchat_app_key">ba509838-d900-4720-85ad-3d37643df4d2</string>



    <string name="freshchat_file_provider_authority">com.zeroone.novaapp.provider</string>





    <!--Assets Fragment-->
    <string name="fragment_assets">Admin Assets!!!</string>
    <string name="my_managers">My Managers</string>
    <string name="selection_list">Assets List</string>
    <string name="category">Category</string>
    <string name="unit">Unit: </string>
    <string name="unit_number">239E-A05</string>



    <!--History Fragment-->
    <string name="fragment_history">History</string>
    <string name="past_jobs">Past Jobs</string>
    <string name="current_jobs">Current Jobs</string>
    <string name="invoices">Invoices</string>

    <!--Account Fragment-->
    <string name="fragment_account">My Account</string>
    <string name="user_name">John Doe</string>
    <string name="user_email">john.doe@example.com</string>
    <string name="contact_support">Contact Support</string>
    <string name="manage_notification">Manage Notification</string>
    <string name="send_referral">Send Referral</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    
    <!--Terms and Conditions Screen-->
    <string name="terms_last_updated">Last updated: %1$s</string>
    <string name="terms_intro_title">Agreement to Terms</string>
    <string name="terms_intro_content">By accessing or using NovaApp, you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions. If you disagree with any part of these terms, you may not access the service. These terms apply to all users of the app, including without limitation users who are browsers, customers, merchants, and contributors of content.</string>
    
    <string name="terms_use_service_title">Use of Service</string>
    <string name="terms_use_service_content">You agree to use NovaApp only for lawful purposes and in accordance with these Terms. You agree not to:\n\n• Use the service in any way that violates any applicable law or regulation\n• Transmit any malicious code, viruses, or harmful data\n• Attempt to gain unauthorized access to any portion of the service\n• Interfere with or disrupt the service or servers connected to the service\n• Use the service to harass, abuse, or harm other users\n• Impersonate any person or entity or misrepresent your affiliation\n• Collect or store personal data about other users without their consent\n• Use automated systems to access the service without permission</string>
    
    <string name="terms_account_title">User Accounts</string>
    <string name="terms_account_content">To access certain features of NovaApp, you must register for an account. You agree to:\n\n• Provide accurate, current, and complete information during registration\n• Maintain and update your account information to keep it accurate\n• Maintain the security of your account credentials\n• Accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account\n• Notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your account\n• Use only one account per person\n\nWe reserve the right to suspend or terminate accounts that violate these terms or engage in fraudulent activity.</string>
    
    <string name="terms_bookings_title">Service Bookings</string>
    <string name="terms_bookings_content">When booking services through NovaApp:\n\n• All bookings are subject to service provider availability\n• You agree to provide accurate property and service details\n• Cancellation policies apply as specified at the time of booking\n• You are responsible for ensuring access to the service location\n• Service providers are independent contractors, not our employees\n• We facilitate connections but are not liable for service quality\n• Payment is required as specified in the booking confirmation\n• Refunds are subject to our refund policy and service provider terms</string>
    
    <string name="terms_payments_title">Payments and Fees</string>
    <string name="terms_payments_content">Payment terms include:\n\n• All fees are displayed before you confirm a booking\n• Payment is processed securely through third-party payment processors\n• You authorize us to charge your selected payment method\n• Prices may change without notice, but confirmed bookings are locked\n• Additional fees may apply for special requests or circumstances\n• Refunds, if applicable, will be processed to the original payment method\n• You are responsible for any taxes applicable to your transactions\n• We reserve the right to refuse or cancel transactions at our discretion</string>
    
    <string name="terms_cancellation_title">Cancellations and Refunds</string>
    <string name="terms_cancellation_content">Cancellation and refund policies:\n\n• Cancellation requests must be made through the app or by contacting support\n• Cancellation fees may apply based on timing and service provider policies\n• Refunds are processed according to the cancellation policy in effect at booking time\n• No-shows or last-minute cancellations may result in full charges\n• Service provider cancellations will result in full refunds or rescheduling\n• Refund processing times vary by payment method (typically 5-10 business days)\n• Disputes regarding cancellations should be reported within 48 hours of service time</string>
    
    <string name="terms_liability_title">Limitation of Liability</string>
    <string name="terms_liability_content">To the maximum extent permitted by law:\n\n• NovaApp is provided \"as is\" without warranties of any kind\n• We do not guarantee uninterrupted or error-free service\n• We are not liable for indirect, incidental, or consequential damages\n• Our total liability is limited to the amount you paid for services in the past 12 months\n• We are not responsible for service provider actions or service quality\n• You use the service at your own risk\n• We are not liable for property damage, personal injury, or data loss\n• Some jurisdictions do not allow limitation of liability, so some limitations may not apply</string>
    
    <string name="terms_intellectual_title">Intellectual Property</string>
    <string name="terms_intellectual_content">Intellectual property rights:\n\n• All content, features, and functionality of NovaApp are owned by us or our licensors\n• The NovaApp name, logo, and trademarks are our property\n• You may not copy, modify, or distribute our content without permission\n• User-generated content remains your property, but you grant us a license to use it\n• We may use feedback and suggestions without obligation to you\n• Unauthorized use of our intellectual property is prohibited\n• Violations may result in legal action and termination of your account</string>
    
    <string name="terms_prohibited_title">Prohibited Uses</string>
    <string name="terms_prohibited_content">You may not use NovaApp to:\n\n• Violate any local, state, national, or international law\n• Infringe upon intellectual property rights of others\n• Transmit spam, chain letters, or unsolicited communications\n• Engage in fraudulent, deceptive, or misleading practices\n• Harm minors in any way\n• Collect or harvest information about other users\n• Interfere with the security or functionality of the service\n• Use the service for any commercial purpose without authorization\n• Reverse engineer, decompile, or disassemble any part of the service</string>
    
    <string name="terms_termination_title">Termination</string>
    <string name="terms_termination_content">We may terminate or suspend your account and access to the service:\n\n• Immediately, without prior notice, for breach of these Terms\n• If you engage in fraudulent, illegal, or harmful activities\n• At our sole discretion, for any reason or no reason\n• With or without cause, with or without notice\n\nUpon termination:\n• Your right to use the service will immediately cease\n• We may delete your account and associated data\n• Outstanding payments remain due\n• Provisions that by their nature should survive will remain in effect</string>
    
    <string name="terms_changes_title">Changes to Terms</string>
    <string name="terms_changes_content">We reserve the right to modify these Terms at any time:\n\n• We will notify users of material changes via the app or email\n• Continued use of the service after changes constitutes acceptance\n• If you disagree with changes, you must stop using the service\n• The \"Last updated\" date will reflect the most recent changes\n• We recommend reviewing these Terms periodically\n• Your continued use after notification of changes binds you to the new Terms</string>
    
    <string name="terms_governing_title">Governing Law</string>
    <string name="terms_governing_content">These Terms are governed by:\n\n• The laws of the jurisdiction where NovaApp operates\n• Any disputes will be resolved in the appropriate courts\n• You agree to submit to the jurisdiction of such courts\n• If any provision is found unenforceable, the remaining provisions remain in effect\n• These Terms constitute the entire agreement between you and NovaApp\n• No waiver of any term shall be deemed a further waiver of that or any other term</string>
    
    <string name="terms_contact_title">Contact Information</string>
    <string name="terms_contact_content">For questions about these Terms and Conditions, please contact us:\n\nEmail: legal@novaapp.com\nSupport: support@novaapp.com\n\nWe will respond to your inquiry within a reasonable timeframe.</string>
    
    <string name="terms_effective_date">Effective Date</string>
    
    <!--Privacy Policy Screen-->
    <string name="privacy_last_updated">Last updated: %1$s</string>
    <string name="privacy_intro_title">Introduction</string>
    <string name="privacy_intro_content">At NovaApp, we take your privacy seriously. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you use our mobile application and services. Please read this privacy policy carefully. If you do not agree with the terms of this privacy policy, please do not access the application.</string>
    
    <string name="privacy_info_collect_title">Information We Collect</string>
    <string name="privacy_info_collect_content">We collect information that you provide directly to us, including:\n\n• Account Information: Name, email address, phone number, and profile information\n• Property Information: Property addresses, sizes, types, and related details\n• Booking Information: Service requests, booking history, and preferences\n• Payment Information: Payment methods and transaction details (processed securely through third-party providers)\n• Communication Data: Messages, feedback, and support requests\n• Device Information: Device type, operating system, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information\n• Usage Data: How you interact with our app, features used, and time spent</string>
    
    <string name="privacy_how_use_title">How We Use Your Information</string>
    <string name="privacy_how_use_content">We use the information we collect to:\n\n• Provide and maintain our services, including processing bookings and managing your properties\n• Send you service-related notifications, updates, and important information\n• Process payments and send receipts\n• Improve our services, develop new features, and enhance user experience\n• Communicate with you about your account, bookings, and customer support\n• Send promotional materials and marketing communications (with your consent)\n• Detect, prevent, and address technical issues and security threats\n• Comply with legal obligations and enforce our terms of service</string>
    
    <string name="privacy_data_sharing_title">Data Sharing and Disclosure</string>
    <string name="privacy_data_sharing_content">We may share your information in the following circumstances:\n\n• Service Providers: We share data with third-party service providers who perform services on our behalf, such as payment processing, data analytics, and customer support\n• Business Transfers: In connection with any merger, sale of assets, or acquisition\n• Legal Requirements: When required by law, court order, or government regulation\n• Protection of Rights: To protect our rights, privacy, safety, or property, and that of our users\n• With Your Consent: We may share information with your explicit consent\n\nWe do not sell your personal information to third parties.</string>
    
    <string name="privacy_data_security_title">Data Security</string>
    <string name="privacy_data_security_content">We implement appropriate technical and organizational security measures to protect your personal information against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction. These measures include:\n\n• Encryption of data in transit and at rest\n• Secure authentication and access controls\n• Regular security assessments and updates\n• Limited access to personal data on a need-to-know basis\n\nHowever, no method of transmission over the internet or electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee absolute security.</string>
    
    <string name="privacy_your_rights_title">Your Rights and Choices</string>
    <string name="privacy_your_rights_content">You have the following rights regarding your personal information:\n\n• Access: Request access to your personal data\n• Correction: Request correction of inaccurate or incomplete data\n• Deletion: Request deletion of your personal data\n• Data Portability: Request transfer of your data to another service\n• Opt-Out: Unsubscribe from marketing communications\n• Account Settings: Manage your privacy preferences through app settings\n\nTo exercise these rights, please contact us using the information provided in the Contact Us section.</string>
    
    <string name="privacy_children_title">Children\'s Privacy</string>
    <string name="privacy_children_content">Our services are not intended for individuals under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children. If you are a parent or guardian and believe your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us immediately. If we become aware that we have collected personal information from a child without parental consent, we will take steps to delete such information.</string>
    
    <string name="privacy_changes_title">Changes to This Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_changes_content">We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page and updating the \"Last updated\" date. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.</string>
    
    <string name="privacy_contact_title">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="privacy_contact_content">If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our data practices, please contact us:\n\nEmail: privacy@novaapp.com\nSupport: support@novaapp.com\n\nWe will respond to your inquiry within a reasonable timeframe.</string>
    
    <string name="privacy_effective_date">Effective Date</string>
    <string name="privacy_read_more">Read More</string>
    <string name="privacy_read_less">Read Less</string>
    
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="app_version">App Version</string>
    <string name="version_number">1.0.0</string>

    <!--About Screen-->
    <string name="about_app_description">NovaApp is your go-to platform for premium home cleaning services, designed for modern living. From general and deep cleaning to sofa, carpet, mattress, and furniture care, NovaApp connects you with vetted professionals who deliver exceptional results. Book services on your schedule, pay securely in-app, and track your bookings effortlessly—all with the convenience of one powerful app.</string>
    <string name="about_features">Features</string>
    <string name="about_feature_property_management">Property Management</string>
    <string name="about_feature_property_management_desc">Easily manage multiple properties from one place</string>
    <string name="about_feature_service_booking">Service Booking</string>
    <string name="about_feature_service_booking_desc">Book cleaning, electrical, plumbing, and repair services</string>
    <string name="about_feature_real_time_updates">Real-time Updates</string>
    <string name="about_feature_real_time_updates_desc">Get instant notifications on job status and bookings</string>
    <string name="about_feature_payment">Secure Payments</string>
    <string name="about_feature_payment_desc">Safe and secure payment processing</string>
    <string name="about_legal">Legal</string>
    <string name="about_contact">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="about_website">Website</string>
    <string name="about_support_email">support@novaapp.com</string>
    <string name="about_developed_by">Developed by</string>
    <string name="about_company_name">ZeroOne Technologies</string>
    <string name="about_copyright">© 2025 ZeroOne Technologies. All rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="about_rate_app">Rate App</string>
    <string name="about_share_app">Share App</string>
    <string name="about_feedback">Send Feedback</string>
    <string name="about_version_label">Version</string>

    <!--Job Status-->
    <string name="status_accepted">Accepted</string>
    <string name="status_started">Started</string>
    <string name="status_ended">Ended</string>
    <string name="status_rated">Rated</string>
    
    <!--Phone Number Input Screen-->
    <string name="enter_phone_number">Enter Your Phone Number</string>
    <string name="phone_number_subtitle">We\'ll send you a verification code to confirm your number</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="country_code">Country Code</string>
    <string name="select_country">Select Country</string>
    <string name="continue_text">Continue</string>
    <string name="invalid_phone_number">Please enter a valid phone number</string>
    <string name="phone_number_hint">Phone number</string>
    
    <!--Phone Verification Screen-->
    <string name="verify_phone_number">Verify Phone Number</string>
    <string name="verification_code_sent">We\'ve sent a verification code to</string>
    <string name="enter_verification_code">Enter the 4-digit code</string>
    <string name="code_expires_in">Code expires in %1$s</string>
    <string name="resend_code">Resend Code</string>
    <string name="didnt_receive_code">Didn\'t receive the code?</string>
    <string name="verify">Verify</string>
    <string name="verifying">Verifying…</string>
    <string name="invalid_code">Invalid verification code. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="code_expired">Verification code has expired. Please request a new one.</string>
    <string name="resend_code_available">Resend code available in %1$s</string>
</resources>